You two look so black today.
I think I'm going to grow that awesome ticker tape.
Positive
So today's NARUTAN is a quiz!
AKB48 Intro Quiz
Quiz Intro Quiz
I don't know what it means anymore.
I'm going to do an intro quiz for now.
Are you confident about it?
Yes, I am.
Yes? Yes?
Do you know the song? Maybe.
I don't think I'd be able to find the lyrics even if I did know it.
It's so self-indulgent.
Why don't you just say the title?
If I could remember the title.
That's right.
We were on stage a lot.
We've toured all over the country.
I've heard a lot of the songs, so I'm pretty sure I can do it.
I'm looking forward to it.
The manager will select the songs for us.
Well, I'll get right to it.
NARUTAO
Let's start with the first song.
Yes, sir.
Which one do you like better?
Hands up.
Hands in the air.
You're being too aggressive.
Okay, here we go.
Dear my teacher
Oh!
I can do this.
I've done this before.
Hey, it's hard.
It's the only thing I did at all when I first started.
But I really liked the guy who danced "Dear my teacher.
Didn't you go all the way?
Dear my teacher was in a good position.
I was so happy.
Some of them were singing in the front.
But the dancing was so good!
The second song was the next one.
Wagamon Collection
Oh wow, you got it right!
Pico pico.
Have you ever done that?
I have.
Really?
I've heard of it.
We did it on the Okayama tour.
You remember it so well.
Did you see it?
I don't know if I was in it.
I don't remember.
Okayama tour
Mature Image
Then the third song!
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes
Run, Penguin!
You can afford it, can't you?
I know what this is.
No, no, no.
Running penguins...
It's so cute!
The outfit and everything.
But it's hard to shake.
It's hard.
The moves aren't cute.
It's not cute.
It's hard
It's cute but the difficulty level is not cute
But the difficulty level is not cute
Yes, it is.
Surprisingly.
I think it's easy to do.
Run, Penguin!
It's so hard!
I asked my teacher why.
I asked him why.
I know it's not an assignment, but...
I heard that it was a wish for the students to dance this hard
I heard that it was a wish for the students to dance this hard.
Then I realized how difficult it was.
I knew it was so difficult.
It's too wonderful!
The thought is too wonderfulThe thought is too nice.
So please pay attention to the performance!
When we do it in the future...
Now the fourth song!
Yes, yes, yes...
Wait, it's not done yet.
What? It's not done?
It's done, but wait, wait, wait.
The title is coming up.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay, okay, good luck.
Okay, one more time, no dividers.
No interrupts?
Why do you say that? Answer me. Answer me.
No, no, no, you can answer.
Go ahead.
Love, uh...
Wait, wait, wait.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Uh-uh-uh-uh.
You're a woo-woo.
It's woo-woo.
Wait, why are the lyrics ready?
It's "uh-uh.
I'm sorry, I just said it.
Love training
Uh-oh.
And you're right.
Let's say it next.
That's a little exquisite, isn't it?
Worst.
That was divine.
You say you'll always love someone, so you'll always love someone.
"You'll always love someone.
I heard it recently at a concert.
I heard it. I did.
I don't know.
Shugendo (asceticism) came up.
Training.
What kind of training? What training?
A little more.
A few more tears.
Okay, next.
Five.
Yes!
Wow!
Yes, jeez!
The wind is blowing.
It's a great song, but we did it together on the Kumamoto tour.
We did it together on the Kumamoto tour, double center, and I did Narita Puji on the Yamaguchi tour.
That's why it was so emo. We did well.
We've done a lot more songs than you'd think.
Yes, we have.
I don't understand this one.
Let's hear it again.
You're right... we're playing the same game now.
What? I've never played this before.
What do you mean?
But I think I've heard of it.
Yes, I've heard of it.
I'm kind of getting the vibe of the song.
Really?
It's a little softer.
Can I tell you something? Don't say it.
I'll tell you what... - A wedding dress for you?
Yes, a sew-along.
That's the vibe, right?
That's it, right? That's the vibe, right?
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
I want to hear some more.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Sing?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I think I know what you mean.
Yeah, yeah, I know that part, too.
I know that sound, too, by the way.
Oh, I really don't know it.
Hey, wait!
But you know what, I can't find a single lyric.
I know the intro.
I know I've heard it before.
Oh, I think I got it.
You don't?
There it is.
Tighter, tighter, tighter, tighter, tighter, tighter.
I'm in a tight spot right now.
Wait, wait, wait.
You know what I'm talking about.
Team One?
No, it's not.No, it's not.
Oh, then it's not.
Hey.
No?
I thought it was this one.
Is it about time?
Isn't that the Team One song?
What was that?
Is this a giveaway?
Oh, I'm so frustrated.
Wait till the song starts.
That's right. Listen until the very last minute.
Maybe it'll come out.
Ending
I'm gonna be in the mood.
I feel like I'm in the mood.
I don't know.
I'm almost giving up on this one too, right?
I'm so frustrated, but I'm curious about the credits, so please tell me what's going on.
me
Me! Myself!
I love this song!
I love this song I'm having them play it in front of me on the Tsukumoto tour...
Yes, give me that
I know you heard it because I didn't sing it, but it stuck in my head.
I only heard the song because I was listening to it too... and I know you've heard it too... it's frustrating... but I guess it makes a difference whether you've experienced it or not...
Wow, Kresit.
Seven minutes, I'm in the seat.
Mmm-hmm.
Ugh, that's disgusting.
What?
Did the difficulty level suddenly increase?
I think it's higher than the first half.
What was that? What was that?
What was that?
But...
But, Maru-chan, you're doing it.
You're doing it?
Yes, I'm doing it.
Do you want to hear it again?
Listen again.
Yes, sir.
Ha-ha.
Ha-ha-ha.
Ah, ah, ah, I knew it, ahh...
I'm in pain, I'm in pain.
What is this?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
He's scary!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Let's get him out!
Chara-chara-chara-chara, what is this?
I'm in pain.
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Oh, I know... three tears, right?
Oh, really?
Oh, three tears!
Wow.
I danced once too.
Miki Mizusawa, Tsugaru
Yay, yay, yay!
Soda at the Rokkatsu performance
That was the first song.
That was when we were all 16.
So it was a while ago.
It was 3 or 4 years ago.
It's already in my mind.
It came out great, great.
That's great.
It took you a long time.
Okay, then.
I'll go next time.
Okay.
Test one, two, three.
Wait a minute... I don't remember this song.
This is cool.
What's this?
It's so cool.
Is this really from AKB48?
You've never played it before?
I've never done it, no way.
But it's a pretty cool song.
Like, "You might step in dog poop there.
That's what I thought.
The song, the title.
Yeah, I've never heard of the song, but...Yeah, I've never heard the song.
Go ahead.
We've come this far.
We're going to Wonderland.
Wow!
This is the song they're playing at Ana's show.
You did?
I didn't, but I heard it.
I didn't know that.
Too geeky for you?
Maniac.
The last few songs are maniacal.
A few songs are maniacal.
I'm in a lot of pain.
But not too easy.
It's boring.
It's just right, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
Yes, ma'am.
Can I say something?
Go ahead.
Even if you're a few feet away.
Oh!
That's a tough lyric.
It was written about 3 years ago, after the Corona disaster.
I was at home, and they asked me to make a video.
I couldn't remember the lyrics.
Oh, yeah! Yes! That's me! That's me!
I tried my best to memorize the lyrics while looking at the markers.
You asked me to send you a video of me singing something.
I did it because you asked me to.
And they didn't use any of them?
No, it's like one of the big 16.
Oh, there was?
It was used in a very, very tiny way.
I'm serious, I'm serious, I'm serious.
I didn't know where I was.
Maybe not.
Tell me it's being used.
I was like, "They're probably using it here.
Oh, really?
There you go.
Here we go.
Ayanan.
I haven't done it.
I've never heard of it.
What?
So you can tell me if I ask you first?
I'll let you know where the com is.
Yes, sir.
I'll run the com.
I'll run the com...
I'll run the com tip, sir.
That's it.
I think I've heard that one before.
I think I've heard that before.
It's a little weird.
It doesn't sound right at all.
No way.
What was that?
Choguri's song came up.
Smile Case
I love, love, love it!
the end
I didn't like it that much
I didn't like it.
I'm the kind of guy who doesn't get out the back of the house.
Every day.
An unexpected story.
I knew it was there!
Oh no!
There's rust!
Rust is finally coming out!
The rusty part... "Poco-bone"...
Poco-boom, poco-boom, poco-boom!
The sound effect came out.
What?
You know what I mean.
Do you want to say it with me?
Yeah. - Okay.
Ready?
Green Flash!
You're not gonna hear this one.
It's actually my go-to song when I'm doing karaoke or something, because I sing it like crazy.
You don't have it? Maybe you don't?
Oh!
Peeta peeta peeta peeta.
What was that?
Peep-ta-pee-ta-pee-ta.
He just spoke.He talked.
Interesting song, huh?
Does it sound funny?
Is it funny?
What bohemia!
Oh, no!
Why, why, why, why...
What!
What?
What happened?
What the hell is going on?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
I don't understand.
LOL!
LOL.
I thought it would never happen.
I just said that anyway.
It's not like it just hit me.
I just thought it was an interesting song.
Oh! I thought, "What's Bohemia?
I thought...
Isn't it a miracle?
It's a miracle!
It's an accessory.
I'm going to play a song that I'm supposed to play at the center of the stage.
Goodbye and Milky.
Wow.
I think there's something amazing about that.
Wow, that's interesting.
I'm a little taken aback right now.
I wanted to hear it.
Let's hear it.
I'll ask you later.
We'll go over this.
We're not going to go over this.
It's not gonna be a miracle.
It's a bit of a miracle.
Oh!
NARUTAO Channel
So, I'm going to do an intro quiz...
What is this miracle?
I was so surprised, I didn't know such a thing could happen.
Moments like this only happen in a moment of time.
I'm glad I was able to capture it on camera.
I'm glad, wow!
I've never encountered this song before...
I've been doing AKB for about 9 years.
I still want to learn more.
That's right.
I'd like you to play Bohemia.
Bohemia? Do you want to?
I was hoping you'd do it somewhere.
It's the only way to do it.
It was a miracle of fate, wasn't it?
So, how many of you were able to guess?
What do you think?
Let's keep listening to AKB songs!
Okay.
That's all for now, this is Naruto.
Bye bye!
ED
Standing around
Reika-san's OLY PLANKTON
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You got it? That's really great.
That's amazing.
I'm so surprised.